foreclosureradar.com 2019-05-29

# Privacy Policy - PropertyRadar

**Effective Date: April 16, 2019**

PropertyRadar, Inc. (“PropertyRadar”, “we”, “us”, or “our”), recognizes the importance of privacy. In this Privacy Policy, we describe how we collect, use, and disclose information that we obtain about visitors to our website [www.propertyradar.com](http://www.propertyradar.com/) and related subdomains (collectively, the “Site”) and users of the services available through our Site (the Site, and services available through it, are hereinafter collectively referred to as the “Services”). The visitors to our Site and the users of our Services are the “Users” (or “You”).

This Privacy Policy only applies to the information that we collect from You through Your use of our Services. It does not apply to the information that we collect from non-Users, such as from public sources (e.g., foreclosure records, county recorder records, courthouse records). This Privacy Policy also does not apply to any third-party websites or applications that may be linked from our Services. Any access to and use of such linked websites and applications is not governed by this Privacy Policy but instead is governed by the privacy policies of those third parties. We are not responsible for the information practices of such third-party websites or applications, and we encourage You to read their privacy policies.

By using any of our Services, You agree that Your information, including personal information, will be collected, used, and disclosed as described in this Privacy Policy and that PropertyRadar may contact You via email or phone for customer support, billing, and other Services-related purposes (e.g., notices regarding disruption of Service). Your use of our Services, and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our [User Agreement](https://www.propertyradar.com/user-agreement), including its applicable limitations on damages and the resolution of disputes.

 **  
Information We Collect  
How We Use Information  
How We Disclose Information  
Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms  
Third-Party Services  
Do Not Track Disclosure  
Security  
User Choices  
Children  
Contact Us  
Changes to this Privacy Policy  
**

### Information We Collect

We collect information about You directly from You and automatically through Your use of our Services:

  *  **Information We Collect Directly from Users.** We may collect information about You directly from You. For example, if You create an account with us we will collect Your name, email address, phone number, and password. If You pay for our Services, we will also collect Your payment card information and billing address. We will also collect any other information that You provide to us through our Services.
  *  **Content Posted by You.** You may post or upload materials to our Services, such as notes, comments, or photos (collectively, “Content”). If a You post Content on our Services, You may choose to make that Content available to other Users and, by doing so, Your name and other information may be available to those designated Users. Please note that once You have shared Content, we cannot prevent such information from being used in a manner that may violate this Privacy Policy, our [User Agreement](https://www.propertyradar.com/user-agreement), the law, or Your personal privacy.
  *  **Information We Collect Automatically.** We automatically collect information about You through Your use of our Services, including, without limitation, IP address, location, browser type, domain name, the website that led them to our Services, the website to which You go after leaving our Services, the dates and times You access our Services, device ID, and activities within our Services (e.g., links You click, searches You run, etc.). Please see our Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms section below for more information. We may combine information we collect automatically with information we collect directly from or from third parties.

### How We Use Information

We use the information that we collect, including personal information and Content, for the following purposes:

  *  **Protecting Rights and Interests.** To protect the safety, rights, property, or security of PropertyRadar, the Services, any third party, or the general public; to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues; to prevent or stop activity which PropertyRadar, in its sole discretion, may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, an illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity; to use as evidence in litigation; and to enforce this Privacy Policy or our [User Agreement](https://www.propertyradar.com/user-agreement).
  *  **Providing and Improving Our Services.** To provide and maintain our Services; to improve our Services; to develop new features, products, or services; to perform technical operations, such as updating software; and for other customer service and support purposes.
  *  **Research and Analytics.** To analyze how You interact with our Services; to monitor and analyze usage and activity trends; and for other research, analytical, and statistical purposes.
  *  **Marketing and Communications.** To communicate with You about Your account and use of our Services; to send You product or service updates; to respond to Your inquiries; to provide You with news and newsletters, special offers, promotions, and other information we think may interest You; and for other informational, marketing, or promotional purposes. Our communications with You may include communications via email or text/SMS. Please see our section regarding User Choices for more information about how to change Your communications preferences.
  *  **Legal Compliance.** To comply with applicable legal or regulatory obligations, including as part of a judicial proceeding; to respond to a subpoena, warrant, court order, or other legal process; or as part of an investigation or request from law enforcement or a governmental authority.

### How We Disclose Information

We disclose the information that we collect, including personal information and Content, as described to You at the time of collection, as consented to by You before disclosure, and as follows:

  *  **Affiliates.** We may disclose information to current or future affiliates or subsidiaries for research, marketing, and other purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.
  *  **Service Providers.** We may disclose information to our vendors, service providers, agents, or others who perform functions on our behalf.
  *  **Business Transfers.** We may disclose information to another entity in connection with, including during negotiations of, an acquisition or merger, sale or transfer of a business unit or assets, bankruptcy proceeding, or as part of any other similar business transfer.
  *  **Protecting Rights and Interests.** We may disclose information to protect the safety, rights, property, or security of PropertyRadar, the Services, any third party, or the general public; to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues; to prevent or stop activity which PropertyRadar, in its sole discretion, may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, an illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity; to use as evidence in litigation; and to enforce this Privacy Policy or our [User Agreement](https://www.propertyradar.com/user-agreement).
  *  **Legal Compliance.** We may disclose information to comply with applicable legal or regulatory obligations, including as part of a judicial proceeding; in response to a subpoena, warrant, court order, or other legal process; or as part of an investigation or request from law enforcement or a government official.
  *  **Aggregate and De-Identified Information.** We may disclose aggregate, anonymous, or de-identified information for marketing, advertising, research, compliance, or other purposes.

### Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms

We and our service providers use cookies and other tracking mechanisms to track information about how You use our Services. We or our service providers may combine this information with other information, including personal information, we collect about You.

 **Cookies.** Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to a computer’s hard drive through a web browser for record-keeping purposes. Some cookies allow us to make it easier for You to navigate our Services, while others are used to enable a faster log-in process or to allow us to track Your activities while using our Services. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if You prefer, You can edit Your browser options to block them in the future. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers provides information about how to prevent a computer from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify upon receiving a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. If You disable cookies, You may be able to browse certain areas of the Services, but some features may not function (e.g., You may not be able to stay logged into Your account).

 **Clear GIFs, pixel tags, and other technologies.** Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a computer’s hard drive, clear GIFs are embedded invisibly on web pages. We may use clear GIFs (also referred to as web beacons, web bugs or pixel tags), in connection with our Services to, among other things, track Your activities, help us manage content, and compile statistics about usage of our Services. We and our service providers also use clear GIFs in HTML emails to You, to help us track email response rates, identify when our emails are viewed, and track whether our emails are forwarded.

 **Local Storage Objects.** We may use local storage objects (LSOs), such as HTML5 and other technologies to, among other things, collect and store information about Your use of the Services. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our Services or to display advertising based upon Your web browsing activity may also use LSOs such as HTML 5 and Flash to collect and store information.

### Third-Party Services

We use third-party analytics companies, such as Google Analytics, to evaluate use of our Services. We also use third-party companies to enhance our Services, such as providing messaging and communication services. These entities may use cookies and other tracking technologies, such as cookies, web beacons, or LSOs, to perform their services. They use these tools to help understand use of, and to improve, our Services, performance, and user experiences. You can learn more about Google’s privacy practices in the [Google Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/); in order to opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites, You can download the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

We use Stripe for payment, analytics, and other business services. Stripe collects identifying information about the devices that connect to its services. Stripe uses this information to operate and improve the services it provides to us, including for fraud detection. You can learn more about Stripe’s private practices in the [Stripe Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/privacy).

### Do Not Track Disclosure

Our Services do not respond to Do Not Track signals. For more information about Do Not Track signals, please [click here](https://allaboutdnt.com/). You may, however, disable certain tracking as discussed in the Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms section above (e.g., by disabling cookies).

### Security

We have taken steps to help protect the personal information we collect. However, no data security measures can guarantee 100% security. You should take steps to protect against unauthorized access to Your device and account by, among other things, choosing a robust password that nobody else knows or can easily guess and keeping Your log-in and password private. We are not responsible for any lost, stolen, or compromised passwords or for any activity on Your account via unauthorized password activity.

### User Choices

 **Correcting or Deleting Personal Information.** You may correct or request deletion of Your personal information by logging into Your account and updating Your information. Please note that we may retain certain information about You as required by law or as permitted by law for legitimate business purposes (e.g., in accordance with our record retention policies or to enforce our [User Agreement](https://www.propertyradar.com/user-agreement)).

 **Opting out of Email Communications.** We may send periodic promotional or informational emails to You. You may opt-out of such communications by following the opt-out instructions contained in the email or contacting us at the Contact Us information below. Please note that it may take up to 10 business days for us to process opt-out requests. If You opt out of receiving marketing emails from us, we may still send You non-promotional emails (e.g., about Your account with us).

### Children

Our Services are not targeted to children under thirteen (13) years of age, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we will promptly delete such personal information from our systems.

### Contact Us

If You have questions about the privacy aspects of our Services or for further information about our data privacy policies and practices, please contact us at [support@propertyradar.com](mailto:support@propertyradar.com).

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is current as of the Effective Date set forth above. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please be sure to check back periodically. We will post any changes, including any material changes, to this Privacy Policy on our Site.
